<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on ParliamoDiPC's Blog</title><link>https://parliamodipc.github.io/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on ParliamoDiPC's Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 15:21:00 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://parliamodipc.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Replit</title><link>https://parliamodipc.github.io/posts/replit/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 15:21:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://parliamodipc.github.io/posts/replit/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been using Replit since it was called Repl.it, when there where only a few languages supported, and every time you wanted to visit a website you had to wait 20 or so seconds in front of a &amp;ldquo;Waking up&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; screen. That&amp;rsquo;s where I started one of my first &amp;ldquo;bigger&amp;rdquo; projects, a failed URL shortener that had its data hosted on MongoDB Atlas. It also hosted tens of my beginner Discord bots.</description><content>&lt;p>I&amp;rsquo;ve been using Replit since it was called Repl.it, when there where only a few languages supported, and every time you wanted to visit a website you had to wait 20 or so seconds in front of a &amp;ldquo;Waking up&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; screen. That&amp;rsquo;s where I started one of my first &amp;ldquo;bigger&amp;rdquo; projects, a failed URL shortener that had its data hosted on MongoDB Atlas. It also hosted tens of my beginner Discord bots.
It wasn&amp;rsquo;t much, but it was great. Open a browser, look up repl.it and then replit.com, click create, write some code and boom! Your website was online.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I recently tried to do that again and was very disappointed in seeing it is not possible anymore. I now apparently need to DEPLOY a project to get the subdomain?? And it COSTS MONEY???
I guess Replit has just become a full-on hosting service for &amp;ldquo;non-sysadmins&amp;rdquo;. I mean, that&amp;rsquo;s not bad at all, I noticed a whole lot of features that did not really exist when I used it and I&amp;rsquo;m sure they&amp;rsquo;re very easy and comfortable to use, but it just feels weird to know I now have to setup apache for 20 minutes on my VPS to create even the smallest of websites.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I guess that&amp;rsquo;s how it is now.&lt;/p></content></item></channel></rss>